Hello, everyone! I'm Hitoka.
Why am I alone today?
I'm going to prank the members!
I love pranking people. I'm looking
forward to it.
What am I going to do?
I'm going to use this.
It looks like a normal plastic bottle.
Can you see it?
There is a hole.
Put water in it.
I put it here.
Then, it won't leak.
If I try to pour water into it,
it will leak.
It's like this.
It's leaking.
I'll do it with 6 members.
How will I do it?
Let's watch it together.
Let's go!
This program is brought to you by six
people who are working to promote
something exciting.
We challenge ourselves to do many
things and make the world a better
place!
Thank you to everyone in PSOUND for
being by our side!
from today, TRIGGER will be back as
Medicare for HUMANs!
Please see the comment!
We are looking for your comment from
everyone!
Let's go!
Yeah!
I was like, ahhhh!
It's amazing!
I think I can do it.
I'm going to start the delivery!
How many people are going to be in the
delivery?
Two people.
Two people?
Thank you for watching!
I'll move the water.
It might be better to move it over
there.
Why is it spilled?
What? What?
What?
Ta-da!
The prank was a big success!
Yay!
I'm glad.
Wait.
I'm scared.
What?
When?
No, no, no.
I was wondering why I was drinking.
I was scared.
When did you know?
I can't believe it.
How do you feel now?
I feel like I was deceived by
Dosstraat.
At first, you didn't lift me up.
No, no.
You were carrying me.
I was carrying you and drinking water.
I thought it was a bad idea.
But you lifted me up and carried me.
I don't know why.
I was carrying you.
I thought I was carrying you.
I moved my parents.
I was carried.
So, the prank was a big success.
It was a prank.
Yay!
So, there are two more people left.
Yes, all of us.
Piyo is the last.
There are four people left.
Only Sakai-san?
No, Piyo-san.
Piyo-san?
I'm thinking of the next one.
What? All of a sudden?
I see.
I see. I understand.
What do you mean?
I mean, I pretend to drink water and
say,
I'm going to do it.
I see.
I feel relieved when I drink it.
I want everyone to feel relieved.
It's difficult.
I'll do my best.
Please subscribe to my Gyo channel.
I'll read this sentence and you answer.
Can I drink water?
Yes.
Thank you for watching my Gyo video.
Could you move the water to this side?
Sorry.
Wow! It's broken.
I'm sorry.
I'll put it back.
How do you feel about your first
anniversary?
It's been a year since I debuted.
I thought it was a short time.
I said I would debut on April 1st last
year.
It's been a year.
But I'm used to it.
I feel like it's been a year.
It's a strange feeling.
It's been a year.
I want to look ahead for a long time.
I thought it was a year.
It's short.
Is it short?
I don't know.
I think it's better to be short.
Really?
I'm going to make a short video.
Please subscribe to my channel.
What do you want to challenge in the
future?
I want to challenge eating a lot, which
we haven't done yet.
I agree.
I think we've never done it together.
I have an idea.
You want to eat a lot, right?
In spring, we have a water drinking
competition.
Oh!
Are you confident that you can win?
Yes.
I have water.
Do you have water for that?
Yes.
Really?
So, I'll challenge drinking water.
Oh, no!
What should I do?
I'll do it before you do.
What?
I'm glad.
I'll start.
3, 2, 1.
2, 1.
It's wet!
What's wrong with you?
I was so nervous.
I thought it was leaking.
What's wrong with you?
I thought it was weird.
It's unnatural.
You said it was leaking.
It's leaking.
I didn't know what was going to happen.
I was wondering what was going to
happen.
What's this?
A prank?
YouTube.
Tokibaro?
What's this?
You're making a big mess.
I was wondering what was leaking.
I was wiping it.
I was wondering why it was leaking.
I was thinking about lifting it up.
You were wiping it.
I was wiping it.
I thought I couldn't lift it up.
You couldn't lift it up.
I drank it.
You drank it?
Do you do this to everyone?
I was the first one to lift it up.
Okay.
It was a prank.
Thank you for watching. Please
subscribe to our channel.
We are going to have a Q&A session.
Please come here.
You will ask a question.
I will give you a pen.
Q&A session
You will give me a pen and you will ask
a question to Kanami.
And Kanami will answer.
Can I drink this?
You can drink it.
I'll try again.
Can you pour more water?
A little more.
It's coming out.
I'm scared.
I'll try again.
It's coming out.
To be continued.
I'm scared.
Everyone.
It's fast.
I'm scared.
I was surprised.
I thought you were different from
usual.
You don't say like, I want to go there.
I was wondering if you were in a hurry.
I thought I had to hurry.
I was in a hurry.
I was surprised.
I was scared.
Are you OK?
I didn't know what was going on.
I was surprised.
You are fast.
Is that so?
Wait a minute.
The tip of the finger can remove the
receiving sparsity!
NEXT TRIP
There should be questions from the
questioners.
Kanami can read my answer and answer
it.
She is talking about something else.
I'll be finished soon.
Thanks for the',
Ok Well
Let's go home.
I'm going to pour it.
Wait.
It's hot.
Did you pour it with that?
Yes.
Open it.
I'm going to pour it.
It's OK.
The water...
Will it be reflected?
Please subscribe to this channel.
Why is it wet?
Let's wipe it.
Do you want to move the water?
Yes, please.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Is this a prank?
What is this?
What?
It was a prank.
I didn't react at all.
I was surprised.
I thought it was a mystery star because
it was wet.
I see.
What's wrong with you?
The bottom of the jiria was up.
I was surprised.
Is there such a mistake?
I thought it was a prank.
Everyone is slow.
I thought it was a mistake because I
drew it.
I thought it was a mistake.
You don't do that.
I don't do that.
I thought it was a mistake.
I waited a long time.
I was told that I had to put it in.
I thought it was a mistake.
I thought it was a prank.
I see.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Please subscribe!
Is it in the order of numbers?
It's in the order of numbers.
So, it's better to move it?
Yes.
It's better to move it.
I see.
Wow, you are in.
It's her turn.
Yay! It's going well.
Yay!
Prank Success!
How was it?
I was like, ah!
How about this one?
Only one.
Ah!
I thought you said all four.
You lifted it up.
Great!
Thank you!
I'm so happy!
I want to prank everyone.
I can't.
Everyone, we just finished pranking.
We did it.
We did it for Aki-chan.
I see.
It's getting bigger.
That's why we did it one by one.
Did you have any doubts?
No, I was reading manga.
I was reading manga.
I didn't have any doubts.
I'm glad that I was pranked.
Great!
Everyone did a great job.
Please subscribe to this channel!
Thank you for watching!
I don't have a destination for my days
and dreams
I love you, love you, love you, love
you
Everything that exists for you
Everything is a
July cider
The night you spilled
I can't forget it at any time
I want to laugh, I want to say it, I
want to say it
I want to erase my painful everyday
The more I cry, the more I laugh
Today is brighter than anyone else
I want to erase my painful everyday
Please like and subscribe!
I can still say it now, even if I'm
lost on why I'm crying
I remember the time we met
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city after the rain is sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day
I play the mario of the rainbow
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city after the rain is sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day
I play the mario of the rainbow
I play the rainbow dress